<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Dysport</title>
    <link href="https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport" />
    <updated>2022-07-03T20:09:20-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Medical Personel</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport</id>

    <entry>
        <title>What is Dysport(r)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Medical Personel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/what-is-dysportr.html"/>
        <id>https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/what-is-dysportr.html</id>

        <updated>2022-07-03T20:09:20-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    What is Dysport(r) Dysport(r), like BOTOX(r), is an injectable neuromodulator therapy. However, this brand is manufactured by Galderma. It is FDA-approved to treat moderate to severe glabellar lines, which are the vertical lines that form between the eyebrows when we frown. These lines can also&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>What is Dysport(r)</h2>
<p>Dysport(r), like BOTOX(r), is an injectable neuromodulator therapy. However, this brand is manufactured by Galderma. It is FDA-approved to treat moderate to severe glabellar lines, which are the vertical lines that form between the eyebrows when we frown. These lines can also be called "devil horns" and "angry 11s". Glabellar lines are "dynamic" wrinkles formed due to muscle contractions that make skin bunch up.</p>
<p>Neuromodulators such as the botulinum toxin protein (the active ingredient used in Dysport(r)) work by blocking the signals from our body's neurotransmitter, acetylcholine (ACh), which tell muscles to contract. The muscles don't respond to these signals and they stop contracting. This means that the skin above them remains smooth and wrinkle-free.</p>
<p>Besides treating dynamic wrinkles, <a href="https://formaesthetics.com/fillers/">Dysport(r) may be used for other aesthetic and therapeutic improvements</a>, such as for chin dimpling or excessive sweating. You can get advice from our board-certified dermatologists or registered nurses about which treatment is best for you.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.realself.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/RS-Botox-VS-Dysport-Header.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" data-cke-saved-src="https://www.realself.com/news/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/RS-Botox-VS-Dysport-Header.jpg"></p>
<h2>Restylane</h2>
<p>Restylane, a synthetic hyaluronic acids dermal filler, acts exactly like your own body's hyaluronic. FDA approved Restylane can be used to treat your cheeks and marionette lines, as well as your lips. When using Restylane to augment the lips, size, mass and natural definition are added without affecting the natural shape of the lip.</p>
<p>Ingrid E. Trenkle MD is proud to offer Restylane Silk, Restylane Defyne and Restylane Lyft. Each formulation is specifically designed to target specific areas of concern. We welcome you to visit our office and talk with us about whether a filler of hyaluronic acids is the right choice for you.</p>
<h2>Different Treatments</h2>
<p>Botox is the same as Dysport.</p>
<p>Dysport may be less costly than Botox. However, this varies between doctors.</p>
<p>Some people may feel that Dysport lasts longer, but Dr. Khetarpal says each type of treatment lasts for about four months.</p>
<p>The formulas for Botox and Dysport are slightly different based on the protein used in each. Dysport's formulation is more likely to spread once it has been injected under the skin. The FDA has approved Dysport to treat glabellar wrinkles. Botox is approved by the FDA to treat glabella lines, forehead lines and crow's feet.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Is it possible to combine Botox and Dysport with other treatments?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Medical Personel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/is-it-possible-to-combine-botox-and-dysport-with-other-treatments.html"/>
        <id>https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/is-it-possible-to-combine-botox-and-dysport-with-other-treatments.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-27T07:44:27-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Is it possible to combine Botox and Dysport with other treatments? Patients often ask for information about additional treatments, such as Botox and Dysport. You can also get injectable fillers that can be used to plump your skin or add volume. Juvederm and Restylane contain&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Is it possible to combine Botox and Dysport with other treatments?</h2>
<p>Patients often ask for information about additional treatments, such as Botox and Dysport. You can also get injectable fillers that can be used to plump your skin or add volume. Juvederm and Restylane contain hyaluronic acids, which is a naturally occurring compound in skin. A patient may receive a liquid facelift when Botox and Dysport are combined. Liquid facelifts are becoming a widely popular option since you can avoid major surgery altogether.</p>
<p>Patients may also inquire about alternative treatments such as chemical peels or hydrafacials. It's understandable that these patients would want the best treatment as quickly as possible. However, each procedure happens on a case-by-case basis. Your dermatologist will err on the side of caution, making sure to complete your Botox or Dysport treatments first. Once all goes well, you can come back for another treatment to treat another problem area at another time.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://fillerscosmetics.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Buy-Dysport-1x300iu.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" data-cke-saved-src=" https://fillerscosmetics.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Buy-Dysport-1x300iu.png"></p>
<h2>Botox results</h2>
<p>You may start seeing results from Botox within a week, but full results can take up to 1 month. Botox injections can last for several months, some even lasting up to 6 months.</p>
<p>Botox and Dysport are for adults 18 years or older with mild to moderate facial lines. To determine whether you are a suitable candidate, your doctor will examine your medical history.</p>
<p>You may not be eligible for any of these procedures if:</p>
<ul>
<li>are pregnant</li>
<li>Have a history botulinum-toxin sensitivity</li>
<li>have a milk allergy</li>
<li>Have a skin condition</li>
<li>Your doctor will determine if you have thicker skin</li>
<li>Are over 65</li>
<li>Take certain medicines</li>
</ul>
<p>Many medications can interact with injection ingredients. These include blood thinners and muscle relaxers.</p>
<p>You should be aware that injections can interact with anticholinergic medications used to treat Parkinson's disease.</p>
<p>Before you stop taking any medication, consult your doctor. You should also inform your doctor about any medications or supplements that you use, regardless of whether they are prescriptions.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What are the possible side effects of Dysport?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Medical Personel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/what-are-the-possible-side-effects-of-dysport.html"/>
        <id>https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/what-are-the-possible-side-effects-of-dysport.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-27T07:43:55-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    While infrequent, mild temporary bruising is the most common side effect. Dysport may cause temporary weakness in nearby muscles and migrates occasionally. Rarely, Dysport can cause a loss of vision or an asymmetry in facial expressions. The injections used will determine the risk. Before you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><img loading="lazy" src="https://fillersupplies.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/dysport-non-english-1-vial-500u.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" data-cke-saved-src=" https://fillersupplies.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/dysport-non-english-1-vial-500u.png"></p>
<h2>What are the possible side effects of Dysport?</h2>
<p>While infrequent, mild temporary bruising is the most common side effect. Dysport may cause temporary weakness in nearby muscles and migrates occasionally. Rarely, Dysport can cause a loss of vision or an asymmetry in facial expressions. The injections used will determine the risk. Before you have treatment, your doctor will talk to you about this. Because the effects of Dysport are completely reversible, any side effects are temporary, typically lasting only a few weeks. For best results, it is crucial to find an experienced injector who has received advanced training to reduce the chance of side effects.</p>
<h2>When Will Form Medical Aesthetics Open?</h2>
<p>Form Medical Aesthetics will adhere to all local, state, and government mandates. We expect to cautiously resume medical spa and injectable treatments during Phase 2 of the Massachusetts phased reopening. We are awaiting a definitive date from Governor Baker. The third phase of Governor Baker's plan will see cosmetic surgery resume. We ask for your patience and understanding as our staff is working diligently to reschedule all surgeries and procedures affected by our closure. Please understand that in order to open and adhere to Massachusetts guidelines, we will need to limit the number of staff and patients we have in our building and extend the time between patient appointments in order to sanitize rooms. We will be able to offer fewer procedures. In order to maximize our provider appointments, we will continue to hold consultations virtually rather than in person, with a few exceptions (body contouring, Instalift, vein treatments).</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Dysport and Botox</title>
        <author>
            <name>Medical Personel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/dysport-and-botox.html"/>
        <id>https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/dysport-and-botox.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-27T07:42:27-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Botox and Dysport injections temporarily decrease the look of wrinkles. They relax the muscles underneath the skin. By relaxing the muscles, the skin on top becomes smoother. Both treatments contain a similar main ingredient, but the trace protein amounts they contain vary. For some, this&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><img loading="lazy" src="https://eternaldermatology.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/botulinum.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" data-cke-saved-src=" https://eternaldermatology.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/botulinum.jpg"></p>
<h2>Dysport and Botox</h2>
<p>Botox and Dysport injections temporarily decrease the look of wrinkles. They relax the muscles underneath the skin. By relaxing the muscles, the skin on top becomes smoother.</p>
<p>Both treatments contain a similar main ingredient, but the trace protein amounts they contain vary. For some, this may mean that one treatment is more effective than another. They are currently being studied to determine their exact differences.</p>
<p>Botox and Dysport injections take only a few moments to perform. The longest part of each procedure is the application and drying of the anesthetic, rather than the injections themselves.</p>
<p>Unless you develop immediate side effects, you'll be able to leave shortly after your appointment.</p>
<h2>Fewer Injections</h2>
<p>Both treatments have different molecular weights. To explain, Botox has a more consistent weight that rarely falls victim to variability. Dysport on the other side has greater variability in size of the active ingredients. This is a significant treatment aspect.</p>
<p>Again, we'll go back to the size of the treatment area; Dysport, which diffuses easily, usually requires fewer injections than Botox to achieve the desired results. Botox's consistency makes it more suitable for precise areas such as the 11 lines that run between your eyebrows. It's also ideal for treating lines around the mouth and under your eyes.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Dysport</title>
        <author>
            <name>Medical Personel</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/dysport.html"/>
        <id>https://automaniacmrk.github.io/Dysport/dysport.html</id>

        <updated>2022-06-27T07:41:53-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Dysport What can you expect during your Dysport appointment? A Dysport procedure is short and sweet. The physician will first clean the area to be treated and then determine where the drug should be injected. The actual injection will take place after that. The whole&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h1>Dysport</h1>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://fillersupplies.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/dysport-non-english-1-vial-500u.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>What can you expect during your Dysport appointment?</h2>
<p>A Dysport procedure is short and sweet. The physician will first clean the area to be treated and then determine where the drug should be injected. The actual injection will take place after that. The whole process takes only a few minutes unless some form of pain medication is used.</p>
<p>The FDA approves Dysport cosmetic injections for the treatment of blemishes referred to as "frown lines" or "elevens." These are wrinkles found in the glabellar area--the region between your eyebrows. However, an experienced dermatologist may use it off-label, or without FDA approval, for other skin issues like:</p>
<ul>
<li>The wrinkles near your eyes are called "Crows feet", or simply "Crows Feet".</li>
<li>Fine lines around the lips</li>
<li>Forehead lines</li>
<li>Excessive sweating</li>
<li>Acne</li>
<li>Some forms of chronic dermatitis</li>
</ul>
<p>And many others.</p>
<h2>Relaxed Muscles</h2>
<p>Botulinum Toxin A is only given in small amounts so that its effects can be severely weakened. This doesn't impact the efficacy of treatment but rather ensures a safe therapy for you. The muscle stops receiving messages and relaxes. This makes wrinkles disappear.</p>
<p>As a short-term treatment, this neurotoxin helps your face look softer, smoother, and more youthful. But in the long-term, it prevents lines and wrinkles from forming more deeply. We are essentially saying that lines won't form if you reduce muscle activity. The treatment preserves the integrity of your skin and continues to do so until you get injections.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.boatclubmedicalspa.com/images/results/img-procedure-results-botox-dysport-06.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>What Are The Complications Associated With Dysport(r)?</h2>
<p>These complications are very rare. They include paralysis of the nearby muscle resulting in temporary loss of function i.e., drooping eyelid, in approximately 2% of injections. Sometimes, temporary headaches and bruising have been reported.</p>
<p>In rare cases, the effect of botulinum toxin may affect areas of the body away from the injection site and cause symptoms of a serious condition called botulism. The symptoms of botulism include: loss of strength and muscle weakness all over the body, double vision, blurred vision and drooping eyelids, hoarseness or change or loss of voice (dysphonia), trouble saying words clearly (dysarthria), loss of bladder control, trouble breathing, trouble swallowing</p>
<p>In a certain number of individuals the injection does not work as satisfactorily or for as long as usual.</p>
<h2>Rejuvenate Your Face Today</h2>
<p>Form Medical Aesthetics understands that your face is sensitive and we make it our priority to ensure you are comfortable. If you're worried about any discomfort during your treatment, we welcome you to come in half an hour before your scheduled appointment time. To maximize comfort, we ask that you let us know when you arrive if you'd like to have a topical numbing cream placed on the area. It allows the cream to fully take effect.</p>
<p>To discuss your concerns and to find out if Dysport is for you, please contact Form Medical Aesthetics.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.galderma.com/sites/default/files/Dysport.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>Do Talk With The Receptionist</h2>
<p>Before you make your appointment, ask the receptionist these questions to know what to expect from the treatment:</p>
<ul>
<li>Is there a large number of Dysport or Botox treatments in this office? Or is this something they just do on the side?</li>
<li>Are they a dermatologist or a doctor?</li>
<li>Are dermatologists primarily cosmetic or medical?</li>
<li>What is the procedure? Does the doctor or nurse inject the Botox?</li>
</ul>
<p>This information will help you to understand that dermatologists are best qualified to take care of your skin. A lot of places offer Botox or Dysport, but it's best to seek care from someone who's an expert in treating skin conditions.</p>
<h2>What Time Will Form Medical Aesthetics Be Open?</h2>
<p>Fechner MD will comply with all state and local mandates. Phase 2 of Massachusetts' phased reopening will see us cautiously resume injectable and medical spa treatments. We await a final date from Governor Baker. Cosmetic surgery is expected to resume during Phase 3 of Governor Baker's plan. We ask for your patience and understanding as our staff is working diligently to reschedule all surgeries and procedures affected by our closure. We will have to reduce the staffing and patient numbers in the building in order for us to comply with Massachusetts regulations. Also, the waiting time between patients appointments may need to be extended in order to clean the rooms. This means we will have fewer available openings for procedures. In order to maximize our provider appointments, we will continue to hold consultations virtually rather than in person, with a few exceptions (body contouring, Instalift, vein treatments).</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://dscbeauty.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/dysport-1.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>Why Are Medical Spa Prices Different Than Physician Office Prices?</h2>
<p>Some medical spas charge for the injection area, not the entire unit. When purchasing Dysport(r) at a medical spa you are actually paying for the Dysport(r) itself, a nurse injector (or aesthetician) to perform the procedure, and a medical director to sign off on the injection. The medical spa not only has to cover their overhead and pay their employees, but they also have to make a profit. Ask the Dysport(r-injector) about how many units were used. Dysport(r), injections may cost you more than you think. With experience, knowledge of the facial anatomy, and proper placement of the Dysport(r) a qualified plastic surgeon can achieve better results at a lower cost per unit.</p>
<h2>Dysport Aftercare Is Quick And Painless</h2>
<p>Aftercare for Dysport is the same as that needed by Botox.</p>
<ul>
<li>Some activity restriction is required in the first few hours after injection to prevent spreading the neurotoxin to distant sites.</li>
<li>Protection of the treated area from infection, trauma and the sun is crucial in the next few days.</li>
<li>Follow the instructions of your dermatologist for post-treatment care.</li>
<li>There are many options for treating post-injection bruises.</li>
<li>To maintain the effects of the drug long term, healthy lifestyle habits and prompt repeat injections are important.</li>
</ul>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://lucypeters.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/10/dysport-NYC-before-after-photo.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>Different Treatments</h2>
<p>Botox is the same as Dysport.</p>
<p>Dysport may be less costly than Botox. However, this varies between doctors.</p>
<p>Dysport may seem to last longer for some people, Dr. Khetarpal states that each treatment is good for approximately four months.</p>
<p>Based on which protein is used, the Botox formulas and Dysport may differ slightly. Dysport's formula is known to spread a little bit more once injected into the skin. Dysport is only approved by the FDA to treat glabellar lines, too. Botox is approved by the FDA to treat glabella lines, forehead lines and crow's feet.</p>
<h2>Clinically Proven Results With One Dysport(r) Treatment</h2>
<p>In three clinical studies of people whose frown lines were rated "moderate" or "severe" by a doctor before their treatment with Dysport(r), 30 days after treatment, the majority (88 percent, 85 percent, and 86 percent in each of the three studies) had their frown lines rated by a doctor as "mild" or "moderate" at a maximum frown. A patient might see a difference in their frown lines from being severe to moderate to mild.</p>
<p>Western Dermatology Consultants, Albuquerque's board-certified dermatologists will gladly discuss with you all our beauty and health skin treatments including Dysport(r). There is a wide variety of rejuvenation methods for all types of skin and conditions--including injectable dermal fillers, which address volume loss and related creases--and we will take the time to help you figure out which is best for you.</p>
<ul>
<li>Dysport(r)</li>
</ul>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://fillersupplies.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/dysport-non-english-1-vial-500u.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>What is the Most Vital Information About Dysport I Need to Know?</h2>
<p>Some people with breathing difficulties may require the use of muscles in their necks to aid them. These patients may be at greater risk for serious breathing problems with Dysport.</p>
<p>Swallowing difficulties can last several weeks. A feeding tube may be necessary for people who are unable to swallow. Food and liquids can get into your lungs if you have severe swallowing difficulties. People who already have swallowing or breathing problems before receiving Dysport are at higher risk for these problems.</p>
<p>Botulinum canxin injections may cause botulism symptoms in some instances.</p>
<p>The symptoms of botulism include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Loss of strength and muscle weakness all over the body</li>
<li>Blurred and double-vision</li>
<li>Eyelids that are drooping</li>
<li>Dysphonia is characterized by hoarseness, change in voice or loss (hysphonia).</li>
<li>Trouble saying words clearly (dysarthria)</li>
<li>Loss of bladder control</li>
<li>Trouble breathing and swallowing.</li>
</ul>
<p>These symptoms can happen anywhere from hours to weeks after you receive an injection of Dysport.</p>
<h2>Everything You Need to Know About Injectables</h2>
<p>Sometimes, taking care of our skin, drinking water, and using cosmetic products are not enough to bring wrinkle-free revitalized skin. Injectables are an excellent, non-surgical way to smooth out our pesky wrinkles. You can add volume to a portion of your face with some injectables. Simply put, injectables are chemical substances 'injected' in strategic areas of our face. Injectables are a way to reduce wrinkles, contour the body and improve skin texture. Although injectables used to be taboo in the past, there have been almost 2.5 million injections every year since 2015.</p>
<p>Injectables are split into two categories: neuromodulators, and soft-tissue fillers. Neuromodulators focus on reducing lines caused by facial movement. The soft-tissue fillers aim to restore volume that is lost as we age, in particular the lips, cheeks and forehead. Botox, Dysport and other neuromodulators may each have advantages for keeping wrinkles away for several months.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.vivadayspa.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/product_shot_bottle_box-300x156.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>We Are Excited To Welcome You Back To Form Medical Aesthetics!</h2>
<p>We would like to thank everyone at Form Medical Aesthetics for their support and loyalty during this difficult time. We have had an extraordinary experience over the past few months and are working to improve our patient experience.</p>
<p>Since the beginning of the COVID-19 worldwide pandemic, Form Medical Aesthetics has taken extreme precautionary measures, in addition to following the most up to date CDC recommendations and state guidelines to maximize the health and safety of our patients, staff and facility. We are committed to providing excellent patient care and will continue to work to ensure that our medical spa and surgical center remain open for business. Please help us continue to protect the health and well-being of our patients and workplace by cooperating with all of our precautionary measures and protocols against COVID-19 at your next appointment, or as you plan for your surgery.</p>
<h2>Botox results</h2>
<p>Botox may begin to show results within one week. However, full results could take as long as a month. Botox injections also last a few months at a time, with some lasting upward of 6 months.</p>
<p>Botox and Dysport are for adults 18 years or older with mild to moderate facial lines. Your doctor will review your medical history and ask you some questions to determine if you're a good candidate.</p>
<p>You may not be eligible for any of these procedures if:</p>
<ul>
<li>are pregnant</li>
<li>have a history of botulinum toxin sensitivity</li>
<li>Have a milk allergy</li>
<li>Have a skin condition</li>
<li>have thick skin (as determined by your doctor)</li>
<li>are over 65 years old</li>
<li>take certain medications</li>
</ul>
<p>Several medications may interact with the ingredients in the injections. This includes blood thinners as well as muscle relaxers.</p>
<p>The injections may also interact with certain medications that affect your muscles, such as anticholinergics used for Parkinson's disease.</p>
<p>Before you stop taking any medication, consult your doctor. You should also inform your doctor about any medications or supplements that you use, regardless of whether they are prescriptions.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://i0.wp.com/affderm.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/botox-vs-dysport.png?fit=780%2C330&amp;ssl=1" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>Is there any difference in the effectiveness?</h2>
<p>Both injectables have excellent success rates with reducing the signs of wrinkles. In a 2019 study, 88% of patients were extremely satisfied with the results after just 30 days. Dysport lasts between 3 to 4 months needing additional treatments to keep the amazing results.</p>
<p>Botox is a safe, effective treatment that can last for as long as 4 months, although it can possibly last for 6 months, depending on the location of the injectable. Botox lasts longer in smaller areas, such as the lips and eyes. The neuromodulator will eventually be broken down into simpler proteins, which will then be absorbed by your body. You'll notice some muscle movement again (with fewer wrinkles), which makes it a good time to book your next appointment.</p>
<h2>What are Neurotoxins (Toxins)?</h2>
<p>These neurotoxins are often used to treat facial expressions such as crow’s feet, forehead lines and furrows between the browns. These neurotoxins work by inhibiting muscle contraction in the "problem area". They are excellent for smoothing wrinkles and preventing them from getting more intense as you age. At Form Medical Aesthetics, we offer Botox, Dysport, and Xeomin as neurotoxin options.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://elevatemd.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/Botox-v-Dysport.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>Smooth Consistency</h2>
<p>It is crucial to see consistent results with injectables. Dysport has a lower concentration of protein to ensure it evenly spreads across treatment sites. This contributes to the natural results we mentioned just a moment ago without fear of lumps, bumps, and other unsightly effects.</p>
<h2>How Much Would It Cost To Treat My Brow?</h2>
<p>These areas are usually treated by Dr. Myers using 75 units Dysport(r). Her charges for this treatment is $250.00</p>
<p>Dr. Myers does all of his own injections.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://images.wedofaces.com/content/images/dysport-391-view1-detail.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>How Long Does Dysport Last?</h2>
<p>Dysport may help improve the look of your wrinkles for up to 4 months. Results of repeat treatments may be comparable to your first use.</p>
<h2>How Often Can I Receive Dysport Injections?</h2>
<p>Dysport treatment should be completed at least 90 days apart. The safety of Dysport has been studied in up to 12 repeated treatments. Clinical studies demonstrated continued efficacy with up to four repeated treatments.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://fillersupplies.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/04/dysport-non-english-1-vial-500u.png" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>Most Frequently Asked Questions</h2>
<p>The first question we are certain you will ask is: Is it safe? Yes. Dysport received FDA approval for treating wrinkles in 2009 and has been used countless times since then. It's also been approved for other medical uses to further prove it is a safe and effective treatment.</p>
<h2>An Natural Look</h2>
<p>Cosmetic treatments have come a long way in recent years. In the past, clients could expect to leave a treatment looking "worked up." That translated into an exaggerated appearance and overdone features. Technology and methods of application have improved to make both more sophisticated.</p>
<p>Today, the goal of therapies like fillers is to deliver invisible results. That is to say, results that don't alert anyone to the fact you've had treatment. This ensures your features stay proportionate and your natural beauty is enhanced rather than distorted.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="http://jonesfamilyskincare.com/wp-content/uploads/dysport.jpg" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>How Long Does It Take Dysport To Work?</h2>
<p>Though results vary, there is typically a noticeable improvement in moderate to severe frown lines between the brows within 2-3 days.</p>
<h2>Which Is More Effective?</h2>
<p>These cosmetic injections are much faster than traditional surgery procedures. You will see results within days. There is no recovery period for Botox or Dysport. After the treatment is completed, you can return home immediately.</p>
<h2><img loading="lazy" src="https://i0.wp.com/affderm.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/07/botox-vs-dysport.png?fit=780%2C330&amp;ssl=1" data-is-external-image="true"  alt="Dysport" width="80%" height="auto"></h2>
<h2>Botox is made of the same protein as Botox?</h2>
<p>Botox is a Botulinum Toxin product manufactured by Allegran. It is FDA approved to reduce the appearance of crows feet and fine lines around the eyes, similar to Dysport (made by Medicis Aesthetics). There are important differences in these treatments even though they contain the same active ingredient.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
